{
    "subject": "Nash_Brennan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jessica_Buchanan",
    "human_readable": "Nash Brennan is married to Jessica Buchanan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9869278073310852,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Nash Brennan and Jessica Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9760860204696655,
            "question": "Does Jessica Buchanan have a husband named Nash Brennan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9219397306442261,
            "question": "Who is Nash Brennan married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9050596952438354,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Nash Brennan and Jessica Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8875192403793335,
            "question": "To whom is Jessica Buchanan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8753914833068848,
            "question": "Are Nash Brennan and Jessica Buchanan in a romantic relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8676608800888062,
            "question": "Is Jessica Buchanan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8408870100975037,
            "question": "Who are Nash Brennan and Jessica Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7908420562744141,
            "question": "Name the husband of Jessica Buchanan."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.594925582408905,
            "question": "What is the name of Jessica Buchanan's husband?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nash Brennan is married to Jessica Buchanan.",
            "html": "yago_30833_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the husband of Jessica Buchanan.",
            "html": "yago_30833_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are Nash Brennan and Jessica Buchanan?",
            "html": "yago_30833_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Jessica Buchanan married?",
            "html": "yago_30833_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30833_53.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Nash Brennan and Jessica Buchanan married on July 12, 2007. Therefore, the statement \"Nash Brennan is married to Jessica Buchanan\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}